Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lindsey-patno-rn-a000a71a2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Geriatric Nursing Bedside Manner Time Management

Certifications

RAC-CT
Registered Nurse
ICD-10 PDPM for Coders
Advanced Cardiac Life Support
(ACLS)

Lindsey Patno, RN

Clinical Reimbursement Specialist

Greater Burlington Area

Summary

Experienced Clinical Reimbursement Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & long term care facilities. Skilled in organization and timeliness with an exceptional understanding of federal and state rules and regulations as it pertains to the Minimum Data Set (MDS) and PDPM.

Experience

Franklin County Rehab Ctr LLC MDS Coordinator July 2017 - Present (6 years 5 months) St Albans, Vermont, United States

I assess potential residents in the hospital or community setting for admission to the facility for Subacute Rehab or Long Term Care. I also have an Advanced Certification in the Minimum Data Set (MDS) which provides clinical reimbursement for the facility.

The Villa Rehab Center, LLC
Admissions Coordinator
October 2017 - June 2023 (5 years 9 months)
St Albans, Vermont, United States

Screens patients for admission to Skilled Nursing Facility; Acts as liaison for Care Managers in the hospital and community setting; prepares clinical information and admission paperwork, and communicates this with the facility's interdisciplinary team.

Northwestern Medical Center Staff Registered Nurse July 2013 - June 2017 (4 years) St Albans, Vermont, United States

Provided direct patient contact to Medical-Surgical status patients on a Progressive Care Unit

Brownway Residence

Certified Nursing Assistant May 2012 - July 2013 (1 year 3 months) Enosburg Falls, Vermont

Education

State University of New York College at Plattsburgh Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2013)